<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<catalog>
    <book id="3">
        <author>Isaac Asimov</author>
        <description>Second Foundation consists of two previously published novellas originally published in appearing in Astounding Magazine (with different titles) between 1948 and 1950, making this the third volume in Asimovs Foundation series. Decades later, Asimov wrote two further sequel novels and two prequels. Later writers have added authorized tales to the series. The Foundation series is often regarded as one of Isaac Asimovs best works, along with his Robot series.</description>
        <genre>Science Fiction</genre>
        <price>79.0</price>
        <title>Second Foundation</title>
    </book>
    <book id="4">
        <author>Gamma, Erich; Helm, Richard; Johnson, Ralph; Vlissides, John</author>
        <description>Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software is a software engineering book describing recurring solutions to common problems in software design. The books authors are Erich Gamma, Richard Helm, Ralph Johnson and John Vlissides with a foreword by Grady Booch. The book is divided into two parts, with the first two chapters exploring the capabilities and pitfalls of object-oriented programming, and the remaining chapters describing 23 classic software design patterns. The book includes examples in C++ and Smalltalk.</description>
        <genre>Computer Science</genre>
        <price>350.0</price>
        <title>Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software</title>
    </book>
    <book id="6">
        <author>Astrid Lindgren</author>
        <description>Ronia is a girl growing up among a clan of robbers living in a castle in the woodlands of early-Medieval Scandinavia. As the only child of Matt, the chief, she is expected to become the leader of the clan someday. Their castle, Matts Fort, is split in two parts by a lightning bolt on the day of Ronias birth. Ronia grows up with Matts clan of robbers as her only company, until a rival robber group led by Borka moves into the other half of the castle, exacerbating the longstanding rivalry between the two bands.</description>
        <genre>Fantasy</genre>
        <price>79.0</price>
        <title>Ronia the Robbers Daughter</title>
    </book>
    <book id="7">
        <author>Dan Brown</author>
        <description>The Da Vinci Code is a 2003 mystery-detective novel by Dan Brown. It follows symbologist Robert Langdon and cryptologist Sophie Neveu after a murder in the Louvre Museum in Paris, when they become involved in a battle between the Priory of Sion and Opus Dei over the possibility of Jesus Christ having been married to Mary Magdalene. The title of the novel refers, among other things, to the finding of the first murder victim in the Grand Gallery of the Louvre, naked and posed like Leonardo da Vincis famous drawing, the Vitruvian Man, with a cryptic message written beside his body and a pentagram drawn on his chest in his own blood.</description>
        <genre>Mystery</genre>
        <price>139.0</price>
        <title>The Da Vinci Code</title>
    </book>
</catalog>
